Guide to the Robert L. Bracklow Photograph Collection 1882-1918 (bulk, 1896-1905) PR 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Alland Purchase, 1
  - Subseries I.1: Alland Purchase: Negatives, 2
    - St. Michael's Church, 99th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1445)
    - [The Collonade, Lafayette Place], [Alfred Benjamin & Co. next door] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1446)
    - [Elaborate house at left of the Collonade, Lafayette Place] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1446)
    - [2 replicas of Columbus' ships in Hudson] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1893 (Item 1447)
    - [Replicas of Columbus' ships in Hudson with U.S. battleship at right] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1447)
    - [The third Columbus ship and U.S. warship] [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1893 (Item 1447)
    - [Columbus statue, Columbus Circle] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 1448)
    - [N. Y. U., Washington Square] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1449)
    - St. Paul's Chapel from Church St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1891 (Item 1450)
    - [Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show in New York, 3 mounted Indians] (D. V. Beekman says he saw this show as a boy and that it was not at Coney Island but at about 93rd or 94th St., Brooklyn, between Greenwood Cemetery and the Bay) [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1451)
    - [Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show in New York, 4 tepees] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1451)
    - [Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show in New York, Indian woman and child with travois] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1451)
    - Eagle Brewery, 347-355 W. 44th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 1452)
    - Eagle Brewery, 347-355 W. 44th St., 1892 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1452)
    - [18th Century stone and clapboard house], 1893 [Century House] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1453)
    - [Century House, Harlem] 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1453)
    - [Indian hunter and dog bronze statue in Central Park] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1454)
    - [St. Paul's Chapel from Broadway], 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1455)
    - [Lioness and peacock statue in Central Park], 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1456)
    - [U. S. Hotel, 198 Water St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 1457)
    - [Buffalo Bill's] Wild West Show in New York [8 Indians before log cabin] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1458)
    - [W. H. Seward statue, Madison Square], 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1459)
    - Old house, 151st St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1460)
    - [U.S. battleship in Hudson], 1890 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1461)
    - [Washington Arch before bas reliefs were added, Washingotn Sq.,] 1891 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1462)
    - [Samuel S. Cox statue, NW corner of Lafayette and Astor Place] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], [1891] (Item 1463)
    - Pelham Ave. bridge across Bronx River [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1891 (Item 1464)
    - Looking north from 119th St. & Morningside Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1465)
    - Portuguese Synagogue, West 19th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1891 (Item 1466)
    - West Brighton Beach [with high tower] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 1467)
    - [Two old Riverside Drive houses adjoining Riverside Wagon & Truck Works, G. Maile] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 1468)
    - [The Golden Swan Café, Geo. Ringler & Co.] [] (Item 1469)
    - [View along New St., financial section. Signs include Smith & Tomson, No. 81; Watts, stationery] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1470)
      This image also appears in Album 10, page 19
    - [City Hall, winter, 1898] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1471)
    - [West side of Broadway between 79th and 80th Sts. Two old houses, 1897. Sign: N. P. Tyson, mason & plasterer] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1472)
    - [Greeley Sq. with bust of Greeley by elevated station, hansom cab in foreground] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1473)
      This image also appears in Album 2, page 81
    - Fountain House, Flushing [Queens (New York, N.Y.)], 1901 (Item 1474)
    - [Old house uptown, and billboard for Blumsteins, dry goods, West 125th St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1475)
    - Spite House, 82nd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1476)
    - Fifth Ave. & 41st St. [west on 41st St.], [before bldg. of N. Y. P. L] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1477)
      This image also appears in Album 7, page 12
    - Supreme Court, Appellate Division, 25th St. & Madison Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1478)
    - [West side of Broad St. south of Pearl] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1479)
    - [Cottage with auto] [] (Item 1480)
    - [Soldier on street], Jan., 1918 [] (Item 1481)
    - [Hotel W. Hampton?] [] (Item 1482)
    - Fire house with horse drawn steamer in front [] (Item 1483)
    - Two old cottages adjoining H. C. Borger's Park Cottage [saloon] [Central Park West and 70th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1484)
    - Boulder marking site of first three meeting houses at Lexington, Mass. [Lexington (Mass.)] (Item 1485)
    - Worth monument, May 30, 1891 [flag draped] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1486)
    - Cooper Street snake [fossil? In rock] [], 1908 (Item 1487)
      This image also appears in Album 13, page 17
    - Thomas Paine monument, New Rochelle. (Old monument on original site) [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1488)
      This image also appears in Album 11, page 2
    - From Lafayette Place [showing Clinton Hall] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 1489)
    - Southwest corner of 34th St. & 7th Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1490)
    - Old Tom's [saloon], [established 1800. T. J. Holahan], Cedar & Greenwich [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1491)
    - [School?] [], 1896 (Item 1492)
    - [Looking down Washington Mews] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1493)
    - [Old one story frame house] [] (Item 1494)
    - First Hebrew Burying Ground [], 1914 (Item 1495)
    - [Dewey Arch] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1496)
      This image also appears in Album 5, page 23
    - [New York Society Library Founded A. D. 1754] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1497)
    - [Ridley's Candles, established 1806. Looking up Hudson from Chambers St. from Elevated station] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1498)
      This image also appears in Album 16, page 14
    - [Bronze tablet on wall, marking site of the Merchants Coffee House, The birthplace of our Union May 23, 1774. Tablet erected in 1914] [], [1914 or after] (Item 1499)
    - [Bronze tablet on wall, marking site of the Merchants Coffee House, The birthplace of our Union May 23, 1774. Close up.] [], [1914 or after] (Item 1499)
    - [McCarthy saloon, 25 Platt St. corner of Platt & Gold Sts. Greenfield Box Co. next door, on Gold St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1500)
    - [No. 80 Maiden Lane under construction] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1911 (Item 1501)
    - Century House, 1890 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1502)
    - [21-23 Pearl St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1503)
    - Hotel Empire, West 63rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1896 (Item 1504)
    - [Up Fifth Ave. to Dewey Arch], Jan. 1900 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1505)
    - Amsterdam Ave. & 92nd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1506)
    - Amsterdam Ave. & 92nd St. (another view) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1506)
    - H. H. Wolter saloon, No. 67 [] (Item 1507)
    - Worth monument and Dewey Arch Columns [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1508)
    - Stone church with tower [] (Item 1509)
    - Fountain at the south entrance to Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1510)
    - Monument to Andre's captors, Tarrytown [Tarrytown (N.Y.)] (Item 1511)
    - Monument to Andre's captors, Tarrytown [Tarrytown (N.Y.)] (Item 1511)
    - Stone church with tower [] (Item 1512)
    - German Kaiser's yacht and crowd at pier [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1513)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 18
    - German Kaiser's yacht and crowd at pier [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1513)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 19
    - German Kaiser's yacht and crowd at pier, another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1513)
      This image also appears in Album 9, page 21
    - Harbor view with mast projecting above water [] (Item 1514)
    - Astor House [217 Broadway] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1515)
    - Looking north of Broadway from just below Cedar Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1516)
    - Fort Tryon Hall from Corbin Place [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1517)
    - Fort Tryon Hall from Corbin Place, 1913 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1517)
    - Poplars above 181st St. and Riverside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1518)
    - Big oak tree, Dyckman St. & Broadway, 1913 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1519)
    - Sloop yacht of N.Y. Yacht Club at Ocean Races, 9/7/95 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1901 (Item 1520)
      This image also appears in Album 15, page 23
    - Sloop yacht of N.Y. Yacht Club at Ocean Races, 9/7/95, another view [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1901 (Item 1520)
      This image also appears in Album 15, page 24
    - Steam yacht [with sails set] at Ocean Races, N.Y. Yacht Club, 9/7/95 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1895 (Item 1520)
    - Astor's yacht "Nourmahal" at Ocean Races, 9/7/95 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1895 (Item 1521)
    - Steamer "Montauk" [Sag Harbor (N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 1522)
    - Eighteenth century cottage with yard, on corner [] (Item 1523)
    - Old New York doorway with shop below [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1524)
    - Bridge under construction, "left side" [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1525)
      This image also appears in Album 10, page 10
    - Bridge under construction, "right side" [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1525)
      This image also appears in Album 10, page 13
    - Tug and group of single masted fishing (?) boats in harbor [East River (N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1526)
      This image also appears in Album 10, page 12
    - Corner entrance of William Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1917 (Item 1527)
    - Old fort (?) on point [] (Item 1528)
    - John Street, toward 191 Broadway, street scene including store of Knox Hatters next to Bank, subway entrance [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1529)
    - Church [] (Item 1530)
    - Church from cemetery in rear [] (Item 1530)
    - Church of field stones [] (Item 1531)
    - Ninth Ave. and 34th St., Institute for the Blind [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1532)
    - Harlem Presbyterian Church next to corner with Metropolitan Dye Works and drug store, 125th St. and Madison [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1533)
    - Bacon House, 1 Park Ave. at 34th St. [Elaborate house on corner, residential section] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1534)
    - City College, Old building on 23rd St. and Lexington [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1535)
    - City College, Old building on 23rd St., another view from cross street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1535)
    - Monument to North East Bastion [] (Item 1536)
    - Monument to North East Bastion, close up [] (Item 1536)
    - Statue at right of entrance to Custom House [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1537)
    - Palisade Yacht Club [], 1912 (Item 1538)
    - St. Paul's Church and cemetery, Eastchester, Bronx [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1539)
    - Church of Holy Communion, Northeast corner of Sixth Ave. & 20th St. Print through wrong side of negative with signs reversed. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1540)
    - Battery Park in distance from ferry in harbor [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1541)
    - "Unveiling a monument" at end of elevated line with steam engine, 59th Street and Central Park South. Store of Horace T. Kline, druggist, in distance [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1542)
    - Bracklow's store interior [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1909 (Item 1543)
    - Flatiron Building from across park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1544)
    - Old house, Boulevard [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1914 (Item 1545)
    - Looking up Broadway to Woolworth Tower, 1914 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1546)
    - Grace Church, looking north on Broadway from 9th [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1905 (Item 1547)
    - St. Peter's Church and cemetery, Westchester Ave., Bronx [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1914 (Item 1548)
    - Hudson River view from piers with battleship, etc. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1549)
      This image also appears in Album 5, page 2
    - Hudson River view from piers with battleship, etc., another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1549)
      This image also appears in Album 5, page 3
    - Hudson River view from piers with battleship, etc., another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1549)
      This image also appears in Album 5, page 4
    - Hudson River view from piers with battleship, etc., another view from pier 21 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1550)
      This image also appears in Album 5, page 10
    - Tall column on hill, flying Hudson-Fulton flag, 1909 [Spuyten Duyvil Hudson monument] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1551)
    - Tall column on hill, flying Hudson-Fulton flag [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], [1909] (Item 1551)
    - City College bldg. on 23 St. & Lex. Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1552)
    - City College bldg. on 23rd St. & Lexington Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1552)
    - Hamilton statue at Columbia Univ. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1553)
    - Residential street corner with high building beyond [] (Item 1554)
    - Dutch farmhouse with snow. Duplicate view. [] (Item 1555)
    - Brick store front, "Twine and netting, " 132 ?St. [] (Item 1556)
    - Little church around the corner [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1557)
    - [children standing on street] [] (Item 1558)
    - [North Presbyterian Church?] SE corner of 155th St. and Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1559)
    - Convent or other Catholic church property from below, 100th St. and Morningside [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1560)
    - Old corner house with G. D. Hassett saloon downstairs at No. 72 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1561)
    - 14th Street, west of Fifth Avenue, with row or arc lights hanging at right [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1562)
    - Church [] (Item 1563)
    - City College building, 23 St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1564)
    - Ladycliff Convent (school?) from Hudson? [Highland Falls, N.Y.) [Highland Falls (N.Y.)] (Item 1565)
    - Church, 47th St. and Madison [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1566)
    - Civil War monument [] (Item 1567)
    - Entrance to old house with porch and vines [] (Item 1568)
    - Fourth Ave. and 10th Street, corner building with Fleischman Bakery and E. Weingreen, furrier, Grace Church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1569)
    - Dutch Reformed Church with Picaut & Besson next door, W. 21st St. between Fifth and Sixth Aves. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1570)
    - Large excavation, for Penn Station, 33rd St. and Eighth Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1571)
    - Corner of John St. and Nassau St. with Goodyear Raincoat Co. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1572)
    - Rural church [] (Item 1573)
    - Dewey Arch [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1574)
    - Replica of Half Moon in river, 1909 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1575)
    - Downtown street corner, Astor House, looking North on Broadway from Vesey [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1576)
    - Interior of old house with fireplace, cupboard and beamed ceiling [] (Item 1577)
    - Church [same as 1530, another view] [] (Item 1578)
    - Washington Square [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1579)
    - Old mill spillway, at end of [7th Ave. subway] line. 180th St. & Bost[on] Post. Rd. [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1580)
    - Old suburban home in large yard with trees [] (Item 1581)
    - Old suburban home in large yard with trees [] (Item 1581)
    - The New York Homeopathic Medical College and Hospital, East 163rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1582)
    - Nassau Street, NE corner of John St. with Morris Goldstein, tailor, on corner [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1583)
    - Distant view of NYU Hall of Fame Building from across the river [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1584)
    - New York Harbor at sunset [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1585)
    - Old downtown business houses, one with removal notice of Miller & Brewer, moving to 279 Pearl St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1586)
    - Back yards [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1587)
    - Battleship in river, 1909 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1588)
    - Entrance to National Reserve Bank, 165 Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1589)
    - Church from below [] (Item 1590)
    - Row of old three story houses with porches and fenced yards on 7th Ave. between 12th and 13th sts. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1591)
    - Sub Treasury Building, Wall and Nassau Streets [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1592)
      This image also appears in Album 10, page 21
    - Old three story building [] (Item 1593)
    - Eighteenth century colonial farmhouse in yard [] (Item 1594)
    - Business street with Wm. Barthman on corner, Maiden Lane & Broadway, East Side [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1595)
    - Maiden Lane & Broadway, close up of building across street, including Wm. S. Hedges & Co. and L. & M. Kahn, both diamond merchants, No. 170 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1595)
    - Old Dutch farmhouse [] (Item 1596)
    - McAleer's Café, corner of South Street and Burling Slip on East River waterfront [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1597)
    - Buffalo Bill's Show. Indian girl on burrow (part of set previously listed) [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1598)
    - Indian on pony, squaw on pony with travois [Buffalo Bill's Show.] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1598)
    - Four Indians on ponys [Buffalo Bill's Show.] [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1598)
    - Garden City Cathedral [Garden City (N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1599)
    - Replica of Columbus ship in Hudson [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1600)
    - Old three story house with porch and fence, Morningside Park and 113th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 1601)
    - Elms at King's Bridge, Broadway and 230th St., May 1893. Old house under trees [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1602)
    - Battery Park Bldg. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1603)
    - Two story house with doric columns in suburbs [] (Item 1604)
    - Hampton House. Two story house with cupola and ionic columns in yard [] (Item 1604)
    - Old stucco house [] (Item 1604)
    - Dutch colonial farmhouse in country [] (Item 1604)
    - Alexander Hamilton statue at entrance to Hamilton Club, Brooklyn. [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1605)
    - Alexander Hamilton statue at entrance to Hamilton Club, Brooklyn. [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1605)
    - Old library, New York Camera Club [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], [1894] (Item 1606)
    - Washington Square, looking north to arch [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1607)
      This image also appears in Album 8, page 6
    - St. Peters Church, Westchester Ave. near Westchester Square [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1608)
    - Tulip tree 225 years old, with inscription, Inwood Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 1609)
    - Furniss mansion, with ionic columns and mansard roof, 99th to 100th Street, between Riverside Dr. and West End Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], [before 1909, Dec.] (Item 1610)
      Furness Mansion similar to Album 15, page 11
    - John St., view west toward 191 Broadway [Knox hat store next to bank and across from subway entrance] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1611)
    - Ninth Regiment National Guard Armory (negative cracked), 141st St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1612)
    - Hamilton Grange [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1613)
    - Hamilton monument on site of, duel at Weehawken [Weehawken (N.J.)] (Item 1614)
    - Bay at New Rochelle from Hudson Park [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1615)
    - Jacob Leisler monument, New Rochelle [New Rochelle (N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1616)
    - Jacob Leisler monument, profile [New Rochelle (N.Y.)] (Item 1616)
    - Monument to Indian battle at Great Barrington, Mass. [Great Barrington (Mass.)], 1905 (Item 1617)
      This image also appears in Album 22, page 15
    - Earl Percy's headquarters, 1775 [] (Item 1618)
    - Capt. Phil Sheridan staff (4 soldiers with horses, before church) [], 1889 (Item 1619)
    - Plattekill Road, 1888 [Marlboro (N.Y.)] (Item 1620)
    - Tree lined stream, 1889 [] (Item 1621)
    - Juvenile Asylum, 177th St. and St. Nicholas Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], [before 1906, Apr.] (Item 1622)
    - Catherine St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1623)
    - Old house and Budd's Mill, King's Highway?, Flatbush [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1624)
    - Hamilton statue [] (Item 1625)
    - West Point Military Academy. [Labelled "Convent on Hudson"] [West Point (N.Y.)] (Item 1626)
    - West Point flagpole and officers houses [West Point (N.Y.)] (Item 1626)
    - Monument at Newburgh [Newburgh (N.Y.)] (Item 1626)
    - Spuyten Duyvel Creek [near Inwood] [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)], 1910 (Item 1627)
    - Washington Headquarters, Newburgh [Newburgh (N.Y.)], 1910 (Item 1628)
    - From Mt. Beacon, looking across Hudson [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1629)
    - From Mt. Beacon, looking across Hudson [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1629)
    - Mount Beacon from Hudson [Beacon (N.Y.)] (Item 1629)
    - Old frame house [] (Item 1630)
    - Colonial entrance to old shingle house [] (Item 1630)
    - Early church in Flatbush [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1631)
    - Early church at Flatbush or Sag Harbor? [] (Item 1631)
    - Hudson Day Line steamer Robert Fulton [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1910 (Item 1632)
    - Tryon Hall vegetable garden, view north showing intersection of Broadway and Dyckman St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1633)
    - Inwood Heights [Magdelen House] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1634)
    - Paterno Castle, Washington Heights [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1635)
    - Paterno Castle, Wash. Hgts., from Northern Ave. or Riverside Drive [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1635)
    - Octagon House, [Dr. Sweetzer's House] 187th St. between Northern Ave. and Fort Washington Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1636)
    - Octagon House, 187th St. between Northern Ave. and Fort Washington Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1913 (Item 1636)
    - The falcon. Central Park statue [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1637)
    - The obelisk, Central Park [Cleopatra's Needle] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1637)
    - Humboldt bust, Central Park statue [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 1637)
    - Italian warship on Hudson, 10/11/92 [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1892 (Item 1638)
    - Robert L. Bracklow stationery store, 85 Maiden Lane [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1639)
    - Old three story stone house [] (Item 1640)
    - Loading hay, Bensonhurst [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1641)
      This image also appears in Album 17, page 5
    - Church of the Holy Spirit (1661), Bensonhurst [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1642)
      This image also appears in Album 17, page 8
    - Church, Newark, N.J.? [Newark (N.J.)], 1917 (Item 1643)
    - Newark, N.J., 1917, Equestrian statue [Newark (N.J.)] (Item 1643)
    - Monument to founders of Newark, 1666. [Newark (N.J.)], 1917 (Item 1643)